Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Press
  - Subseries C: Productions
    - Beckett plays New York Times Nov 29, 1990 mention of "The Lost Ones" (Box 46, Folder 1812)
    - The B. Beaver Animation / Come and Go review by Bonnie Marranca (typed draft with corrections), undated (Box 46, Folder 1813)
    - The B. Beaver Animation Soho Weely News Dec 12, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1814)
    - The B. Beaver Animation various publications Feb-May 1975 New York, Boston, Chicago, Minneapolis (Box 46, Folder 1815)
    - The B. Beaver Animation / Come and Go Saturday Review Feb 8, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1816)
    - The B. Beaver Animation various publications Mar-Apr 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1817)
    - The B. Beaver Animation Minneapolis Star and Tribune Jun 12, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1818)
    - The B. Beaver Animation various publications May-Aug 1990 (Box 46, Folder 1819)
    - The B. Beaver Animation unidentified clipping, undated (Box 46, Folder 1820)
    - The Bribe various publications, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 1821)
    - The Bribe various publications Jun 1994 Singapore tour (Box 46, Folder 1822)
    - Cascando various publications Apr, Nov 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1823)
    - Cascando various publications Aug-Sep 1976 European press (Box 46, Folder 1824)
    - Cascando program, [1976] (Box 46, Folder 1825)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Feb-Mar 1983 New York press (Box 46, Folder 1826)
    - Cold Harbor Newsweek Mar 21, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1827)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Apr 16-23, 1984 American Cultural Center, Paris, reviews, program, flyer, poster (Box 46, Folder 1828)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Sep, Nov 1984 SUNY Purchase (Box 46, Folder 1829)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Jul-Aug 1985 Kent State (Box 46, Folder 1830)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Oct-Nov 1985 fall tour (Box 46, Folder 1831)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Feb-Mar 1986 Atlanta, Charleston, Burlington (Box 46, Folder 1832)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Fall 1986 Iowa tour (Box 46, Folder 1833)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Fall 1986 Missouri tour (Box 46, Folder 1834)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Jan 1987 West Coast tour [includes program] (Box 46, Folder 1835)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Mar-Apr 1987 New York press (Box 46, Folder 1836)
    - Cold Harbor various publications May 1987 Valladolid, Spain (Box 46, Folder 1837)
    - Cold Harbor Philadelphia Inquirer Aug 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1838)
    - Cold Harbor various publications Aug 1989 Mexico City Arts Festival (Box 46, Folder 1839)
    - Cold Harbor / Hajj American Theatre Apr 1991 (Box 46, Folder 1840)
    - Company various publications Jan 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1841)
    - Company various publications Aug 1983 non-NY press (Box 46, Folder 1842)
    - Company various publications Oct 1986 Iowa press (Box 46, Folder 1843)
    - Company Austin American Statesman Sep 22, 24, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1844)
    - Company Journal de Geneve Apr 17, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 1845)
    - Dead End Kids press package, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 1846)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Nov 1980 (Box 46, Folder 1847)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Dec 1980 (Box 46, Folder 1848)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Jan-May 1981 (Box 46, Folder 1849)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Amsterdam 1981, Hiroshima 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 46, Folder 1850)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Mar, May 1981 Toronto press (Box 46, Folder 1851)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Feb-Mar 1982 includes Minneapolis, Seattle press (Box 46, Folder 1852)
    - Dead End Kids Theater Summer/Fall 1982 (Box 46, Folder 1853)
    - Dead End Kids In Focus Jan 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1854)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Feb 1983 Philadelphia press (Box 46, Folder 1855)
    - Dead End Kids various publications May 1983 Charleston, SC press (Box 46, Folder 1856)
    - Dead End Kids Art Com Spring 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1857)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Feb 1984 Los Angeles press, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1858)
    - Dead End Kids Olympic Arts Festival at Mark Taper Forum Jun 1-Aug 12 1984 festival program (Box 46, Folder 1859)
    - Dead End Kids On Stage New York (Italian) Jul 1985 (Box 46, Folder 1860)
    - Dead End Kids (film) Village Voice, Rolling Stone Mar, Jun 1985 (Box 46, Folder 1861)
    - Dead End Kids (film) various publications Sep 1986 Toronto Film Festival (Box 46, Folder 1862)
    - Dead End Kids (film) various publications Oct-Nov 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1863)
    - Dead End Kids (film) various publications Jan-Oct 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1864)
    - Dead End Kids advertisements Apr-May 1987 Apple Corps Theatre (Box 46, Folder 1865)
    - Dead End Kids unidentified clippings, undated (Box 46, Folder 1866)
    - Dressed Like an Egg various publications May 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1867)
    - Dressed Like an Egg NY Times, Wisdoms Child Sep-Oct 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1868)
    - Dressed Like an Egg various publications Mar, Aug/Sep 1978 (Box 46, Folder 1869)
    - Dressed Like an Egg various publications Mar 1980 Tasmanian and Australian press (Box 46, Folder 1870)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications May-Aug 1985 Boston press (Box 46, Folder 1871)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications Jun 1985-Jan 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 46, Folder 1872)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications Feb-Jul 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1873)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications miscellaneous/unidentified press, 1987-1990 (Box 46, Folder 1874)
    - Hajj various publications Jun-Oct 1982 (Box 46, Folder 1875)
    - Hajj various publications Jan-Oct 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1876)
    - Hajj various publications Apr, Jul, Aug 1984 (Box 46, Folder 1877)
    - Hajj various publications Aug 1984 Japan tour press (Box 46, Folder 1878)
    - Hajj various publications Jun-Sep 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1879)
    - Hajj various publications Oct 1986 Minnesota press (Box 46, Folder 1880)
    - Help Wanted various publications Feb 1986 NY reviews (Box 46, Folder 1881)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Village Voice Jun 26, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 1882)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Industrial Design Sep/Oct 1984 (Box 46, Folder 1883)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine various publications May-Jul 1985 (Box 46, Folder 1884)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine EAR magazine Fall 1985 (Box 46, Folder 1885)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine various publications Apr 1986 MIT performance (Box 46, Folder 1886)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine The Daily Iowan Oct 2, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1887)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine various publications Apr 1987 Florida press (Box 46, Folder 1888)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine New York News, undated (Box 46, Folder 1889)
    - In the Jungle of Cities various publications Nov-Dec 1991 (Box 47, Folder 1890)
    - It's a Man's World various publications Aug-Sep 1985 (Box 47, Folder 1891)
    - It's a Man's World various publications Sep-Oct 1985 (Box 47, Folder 1892)
    - It's a Man's World various publications May 1987 Apple Corps Theatre (Box 47, Folder 1893)
    - It's a Man's World various publications Jun 1987 Apple Corps Theatre (Box 47, Folder 1894)
    - Lear various publications Sep-Dec 1987 Theatrical Outfit, Atlanta (Box 47, Folder 1895)
    - Lear various publications Dec 1987-Jan 1988 New Jersey press, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 1896)
    - Lear various publications Feb-Jun 1988 (Box 47, Folder 1897)
    - Lear various publications Jul-Aug 1988 Storm King press (Box 47, Folder 1898)
    - Lear various publications Nov-Dec 1988 (Box 47, Folder 1899)
    - Lear West Side Spirit, Union News Jan, Mar 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1900)
    - Lear Theater Group Dec 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1901)
    - Lear various publications Jan 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1902)
    - Lear various publications Feb 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1903)
    - Lear various publications Mar 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1904)
    - Lear Dramatics Oct 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1905)
    - Lear The Sunday Star-Ledger Dec 30, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1906)
    - Lear Théâtre/Public May-Jun 1991 (Box 47, Folder 1907)
    - Lear Toronto Star Mar 19, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1908)
    - Lear Theatre Journal no. 45 "Mabou Mines's Lear: A Narrative of Collective Authorship" by Iris Smith, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 1909)
    - Lear various publications miscellaneous/unidentified press, undated (Box 47, Folder 1910)
    - MahabharANTa various publications, 1992-1993 (Box 47, Folder 1911)
    - Mercier and Camier various publications, 1978-1979 (Box 47, Folder 1912)
    - The Mormon Project various publications, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 1913)
    - Mother various publications, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 1914)
    - Peter and Wendy Post and Courier (South Carolina) May 29, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 1914a)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1915)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice New York Times May 1980 Frank Rich review, correspondence (Box 47, Folder 1916)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications May-Aug 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1917)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Aug-Oct 1980 San Francisco and Europe press (Box 47, Folder 1918)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice International Herald Tribune Oct 17, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1919)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Scena Oct 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1920)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Mar-Apr 1981 (Box 47, Folder 1921)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice The Times (London), Financial Times Aug-Sep 1982 (Box 47, Folder 1922)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Aug 1984 Japan press (Box 47, Folder 1923)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Mar, Aug 1985 (Box 47, Folder 1924)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice / Hajj Village Voice May 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1925)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications May-Jun 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1926)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Village Voice Apr 14, 1987 advertisement (Box 47, Folder 1927)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Twin Cities Reader Feb-Mar 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1928)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications miscellaneous/unidentified press, undated (Box 47, Folder 1929)
    - Pretty Boy various publications Jun 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1930)
    - Pretty Boy various publications Jul 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1931)
    - Re-Cher-Chez various publications, 1980-1982 (Box 47, Folder 1932)
    - The Red Horse Animation New York Times Nov 20, 1970 [includes program] (Box 47, Folder 1933)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Oct-Nov 1971 Minneapolis, Seattle, Tacoma press (Box 47, Folder 1934)
    - The Red Horse Animation Phoenix Dec 2, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 1935)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Nov 1971-Feb 1972 California press, 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 1936)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Jan-Feb 1972 Oregon press (Box 47, Folder 1937)
    - The Red Horse Animation The Commercial Appeal (Memphis) Mar 11, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1938)
    - Come and Go / The Red Horse Animation / The B. Beaver Animation New York Times Apr 22, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1939)
    - The Red Horse Animation New York magazine May 15, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1940)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Dec 1972 Netherlands press (Box 47, Folder 1941)
    - The Red Horse Animation Financial Times (London) Jan 4, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1942)
    - The Red Horse Animation / The B. Beaver Animation various publications NY performances, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1943)
    - The Red Horse Animation New York Times Jul 30, 1974 re: Connecticut festival (Box 47, Folder 1944)
    - The Red Horse Animation Soho Weely News May 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1945)
    - The Red Horse Animation Village Voice Nov 19, 1979 re: Animations playscript (Box 47, Folder 1946)
    - The Red Horse Animation unidentified clipping, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1947)
    - The Red Horse Animation DISSENT Fall 1987 "Individuals and Autonomists" by Ellen Levy (Box 47, Folder 1948)
    - The Red Horse Animation San Francisco Examiner 1/12/?, undated (Box 113, Folder 2372)
    - Reel to Real ASU West Thunder Press Dec 8, 1993 [includes ASU flyers] (Box 47, Folder 1949)
    - Reel to Real American Theatre Apr 1994 (Box 47, Folder 1950)
    - Reel to Real Village Voice, NY Times Apr 1994 advertisements (Box 47, Folder 1951)
    - Reel to Real various publications Apr 1994 (Box 47, Folder 1952)
    - Reel to Real various publications Sep 1994 Duke University performance (Box 47, Folder 1953)
    - Reel to Real American Theatre Nov 1994 (Box 47, Folder 1954)
    - The Saint and the Football Players various publications, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1955)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Saturday Review Sep 20, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1956)
    - The Saint and the Football Players various publications Feb 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1957)
    - The Saint and the Football Players The Villager Jul 22, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1958)
    - The Saint and the Football Players various publications summer 1976 European press (Box 47, Folder 1959)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Soho Weely News Dec 12, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1960)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Village Voice Aug 2, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1961)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various publications Jan-Apr 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1962)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various publications Feb-May 1978 (Box 47, Folder 1963)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Semiotext(e) Oct 20, 1978 proof (Box 47, Folder 1964)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation New Haven Advocate Apr 18, 1979 (Box 47, Folder 1965)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation New Statesman Aug 1, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 1966)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various publications Dec 1985 Minnesota press (Box 47, Folder 1967)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation City Pages (Minneapolis) Oct 7, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 1968)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema various publications Jun-Jul 1980 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1969)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema / A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Aug-Sep 1980 Los Angeles press (Box 47, Folder 1970)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema La Libre Belgique (Brussels) Sep 29, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 1971)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema The Yale Herald Apr 24, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 1972)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema (book) Theatre Times Jan 1988 (Box 47, Folder 1973)
    - Southern Exposure various publications Feb-Mar 1979 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1974)
    - Southern Exposure various publications Feb-May 1979 listings (Box 47, Folder 1975)
    - Southern Exposure various publications Jun-Oct 1979 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1976)
    - Starcock various publications Dec 1985-Jan 1986 reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 1977)
    - Sueños La Jornada Aug 28, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 1978)
    - Sueños various publications Oct 1988 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1979)
    - Sueños Art News Jan 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1980)
    - Sueños various publications Feb-Mar 1989 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1981)
    - Sueños miscellaneous/unidentified press, 1985, 1986, undated (Box 47, Folder 1982)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Feb-Apr 1984 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1983)
    - Through the Leaves various publications May-Jun 1984 reviews (Box 47, Folder 1984)
    - Through the Leaves [La Gazzetta?] Jul 10, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1985)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Jul-Dec 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1986)
    - Through the Leaves various publications miscellaneous press with photocopy order forms, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1987)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Apr-May 1985 Montreal press (Box 47, Folder 1988)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Jun 1985-Jan 1986 Montreal press (Box 47, Folder 1989)
    - Through the Leaves Washington Review Aug/Sep 1985 (Box 47, Folder 1990)
    - Through the Leaves unidentified publication Japanese press, unknown (Box 47, Folder 1991)
    - Through the Leaves unidentified publication Israeli press, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1992)
    - Through the Leaves (reconstruction) various publications Sep-Oct 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1993)
    - Vanishing Pictures various publications Feb-Mar 1980, Jan 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 47, Folder 1994)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Jun-Aug 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1995)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Sep 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1996)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Oct-Nov 1986 (Box 47, Folder 1997)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Apr 1991 Geneva press (Box 47, Folder 1998)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Jan 1993 Kansas press (Box 47, Folder 1999)
    - Wrong Guys various publications May 1981 (Box 47, Folder 2000)
    - Wrong Guys Zone magazine Fall/Winter 1981 feature (Box 47, Folder 2001)
    - Wrong Guys PAJ vol. 6, no. 1 piece by Ruth Maleczech, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 2002)
    - The Gospel at Colonus production history, press quotes, awards, undated (Box 48, Folder 2003)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Jul 1982 Minneapolis press (Box 48, Folder 2004)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Aug-Sep 1982 (Box 48, Folder 2005)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Aug-Sep 1982 UK press (Box 48, Folder 2006)
    - The Gospel at Colonus New York Times Nov 11, 12, 1983 Pareles and Gussow reviews (Box 48, Folder 2007)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Nov-Dec 1983 (Box 48, Folder 2008)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications tour press, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 2009)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 2010)
    - The Gospel at Colonus Back Stage Jul 20, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 2011)
    - The Gospel at Colonus America's Arena, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 2012)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications re: television broadcast, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 2013)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications tour press, 1985-1986 (Box 48, Folder 2014)
    - The Gospel at Colonus Arts Review vol. 3, no. 3, Spring 1986 (Box 48, Folder 2015)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 2016)
    - The Gospel at Colonus ELLE Feb 1988 (Box 48, Folder 2017)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Mar 1988 re: Broadway premiere (Box 48, Folder 2018)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Apr 1988 re: Broadway (Box 48, Folder 2019)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications May 1988 re: Broadway (Box 48, Folder 2020)
    - The Gospel at Colonus May 16, 1988 Breuer's letter declining Tony nomination (Box 48, Folder 2021)
    - The Gospel at Colonus plays INTERNATIONAL Jun-Jul 1988 (Box 48, Folder 2022)
      - Villager Downtown Theater Awards, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 1696)
    - The Gospel at Colonus Village Voice Jul 17, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 2023)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Oct 1990 California press (Box 48, Folder 2024)
    - The Gospel at Colonus OC Weekly Feb 28-Mar 6, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 2025)
    - Lulu various publications, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 2026)
    - Prisoner of Love various publications Jun 1995 (Box 48, Folder 2027)
    - Warrior Ant Village Voice Jun 4, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 2028)
    - Warrior Ant Theater Spring 1987 also: Akalaitis's "Green Card" (Box 48, Folder 2029)
    - Warrior Ant Village Voice Aug 30, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 2030)
    - Warrior Ant various publications Oct-Nov 1988 (Box 48, Folder 2031)
    - Warrior Ant American Theatre Jun 1991 (Box 48, Folder 2032)
- Series XI: Objects
  Objects and props from Mabou Mines productions. Of particular interest are the puppets Rose [ Shaggy Dog Animation] and John [ Prelude to Death in Venice], and the shadow puppets from the MahabharANTa.
  - Geiger counter Dead End Kids, undated (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0001)
  - Steinite tube radio/amplifier Dead End Kids, undated (Object 133.2.0002)
  - Glass x-ray slides Dead End Kids, undated (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0003)
  - Hand mirrors Dressed Like an Egg, undated (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0004)
  - Light shoes Dressed Like an Egg, undated (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0005)
  - Painting of woman at mirror Dressed Like an Egg, undated (Object 133.2.0006)
  - Celastic dress by Ree Morton Dressed Like an Egg, Undated; 133.2.0007; 1 item one dress (Object 133.2.0007)
    Dress is large and difficult to move. Access is contingent on curatorial approval.
    Artist: Ree Morton
    Props (object genres)
  - Celastic scarf by Ree Morton Dressed Like an Egg, Undated; 133.2.0008; 1 item one scarf (Object 133.2.0008)
  - Celastic scarf by Ree Morton Dressed Like an Egg, Undated; 133.2.0009; 1 item one scarf (Object 133.2.0009)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0010)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0011)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0012)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0013)
  - Tragedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0014)
  - Tragedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0015)
  - Tragedy mask The Mormon Project, undated (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0016)
  - Red Horse mounts The Red Horse Animation, undated (Box 159)
  - Sueños designs Sueños, 1988 (Box 159)
  - Sueños model pieces Sueños, undated (Box 162, Folder 133.2.0019)
  - Painted celastic swaths Dressed Like an Egg [?], Undated; 133.2.0020; 2 items two pieces of painted celastic fabric (Object 133.2.0020)
  - Rose The Shaggy Dog Animation, undated (Object 133.2.0021)
    Scope and Content note
    Dummy with extra clothing in case.
  - John A Prelude to Death in Venice, undated (Object 133.2.0022)
  - Airplane shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0023)
  - Building shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0024)
  - Tank shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0025)
  - Arrows MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0026)
  - Spider MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0027)
  - Spider shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0028)
  - Antjuna MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0029)
  - Chariot MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0030)
  - Traditional female dancers MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0031)
  - Bowmen MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0032)
  - Antjuna with bow MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0033)
  - Gundul and Wajil MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0034)
  - Dragonfly MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0035)
  - Small female insect MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0036)
  - Crest MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0037)
  - Insect wings MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0038)
  - Flower MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0039)
  - Sword MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0040)
  - Wrenches MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0041)
  - Arrow MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0042)
  - Telephone MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0043)
  - Female reptiles MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0044)
  - Ape MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0045)
  - Rat MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0046)
  - Boar MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0047)
  - Alligator MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0048)
  - Camel MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0049)
  - Reptile MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0050)
  - Frog MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0051)